Guide to the Tamiment Library Newspapers PERIODICALS.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- N
  - New York City Star Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Hard Rain, Inc., 1973-1976 (Box 101)
  - New York Culinarian Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Hotel & Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union. Local 22 (New York, N.Y.), 1975-1979 (Box 279)
  - New York Democratic Socialist Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: NY Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee, 1980-1987 (Box 238)
  - The New York Element Place of publication: New York, N.Y., 1968-1972 (Box 279)
  - New York Feminist Manhattan Tribune Place of publication: New York, N.Y., 1970 (Box 278)
  - New York Free Press Place of publication: New York, N.Y., 1968-1969 (Box 279)
  - New York Generator Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Communications Workers of America, Local 1101, AFL/CIO, 1958-1986 (Box 280)
  - New York Herald Tribune Place of publication: New York, N.Y., 1969-1970 (Box 279)
  - New York High School Free Press Place of publication: New York, N.Y., 1968-1970 (Box 281)
  - The New York Longshoreman: Official Organ of the AFL International Longshoremen's Association Place of publication: Brooklyn, N.Y. Publisher: AFL International Longshoremen's Association, 1953-1954 (Box 281)
  - New York Painter and Decorator Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Rank and File Inter-Club Conference, 1936-1937 (Box 281)
  - New York State Service Employee Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: New York State Service Employees Council AFL-CIO, 1977-1982 (Box 281)
  - New York Teacher Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: United Federation of Teachers, 1993-current (Box 286-286H)
  - New York Teacher Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: New York State United Teachers, 2000-2010 (Box 287-287C)
  - New York Teacher: Official Publication of New York State United Teachers Place of publication: Albany, N.Y. Publisher: New York State United Teachers, 1972-2000 (Box 284-284L)
  - New York Teacher. UFT Bulletin Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: New York State United Teachers, 1978-1993 (Box 285-285D)
  - New York Teacher News Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Teachers Union of New York, 1943-1963 (Box 289)
  - New York Workers' News and Perspective Place of publication: Brooklyn, N.Y. Publisher: Pasternack, A., 1976-1978 (Box 293)
  - New York World-Telegram and the Sun Place of publication: New York, N.Y., 1950 (Box 487)
  - News: Not a Penny on the Rent Place of publication: Great Britain Publisher: United Tenants Action Committee, nd (Box 293)
  - News & Letters Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: News & Letters, 1980-2007 (Box 295)
  - News and Views Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: International Printing and Graphic Communications Union, 1969-1983 (Box 293-294)
    Researchers must use microfilm (Film R-7033)
  - News for a People's World: Reporting for Social Change in Northern California Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif. Publisher: Pacific Pub. Foundation, 1995 (Box 281)
  - News from Nowhere Place of publication: Dekalb, Ill., 1969-1971 (Box 296)
  - News from Vietnam Place of publication: Montreal, Canada Publisher: Association of Vietnamese Patriots in Canada, 1972-1973 (Box 296)
  - The News Line Place of publication: London, England Publisher: Young Socialists, 1976-1980 (Box 301)
  - News of Greece Place of publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: U.S. Committee for Democracy in Greece, 1971 (Box 296)
  - News of Southern Summer School for Women Workers in Industry Place of publication: Baltimore, Md. Publisher: Southern Summer School for Women Workers in Industry, 1931 (Box 301)
  - News Service - American Postal Workers Union Place of publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: American Postal Workers Union, 1975-2002 (Box 298-300)
  - The Newsletter Place of publication: London, England Publisher: Newsletter, 1962-1969 (Box 297)
  - Newsletter Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Center for United Labor Action, 1972 (Box 296)
  - Newsletter Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Japanese American Committee for Democracy, 1943-1947 (Box 296)
  - Newsletter Place of publication: Waltham, Mass. Publisher: National Strike Information Center, 1970 (Box 293)
  - Newsletter of the National Federation of Housestaff Organization Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: National Federation of Housestaff Organization, 1988 (Box 183)
  - The Newspaper Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Committee for a Democratic Society, Rockefeller University, 1968-1969 (Box 296)
  - The Next Step Place of publication: Heidelberg, Germany Publisher: S.C., 1970-1971 (Box 163)
  - NFSSE Forum Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: National Federation of Social Service Employees, 1968 (Box 296)
  - Nickel Review Place of publication: Syracuse, N.Y. Publisher: Nickel Review, 1969-1971 (Box 296)
  - Nigerian Socialist Place of publication: Ibadan, Nigeria Publisher: O. Oni, 1967-1968 (Box 296)
  - Nitzotz = Nitsots Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Radical Zionist Alliance, 1973 (Box 296)
  - NMU Pilot Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: National Maritime Union of America, 1954-1988 (Box 248-252)
  - NMU Rank and File Pilot Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: National Maritime Union, 1953-1955 (Box 488)
  - No Limits Place of publication: Madison, Wis. Publisher: Dream World Dragon Press, 1976-1980 (Box 296)
  - No More Teachers Dirty Looks Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif. Publisher: Bay Area Radical Teachers Organ Committee, 1970-1975 (Box 302)
  - NOLA Express Place of publication: New Orleans, La., 1972-1974 (Box 302)
  - No-Register Guard Place of publication: Eugene, Or. Publisher: Coalition Opposing Registration and the Draft (CORD) (Box 302)
  - Norfolk Gorilla Place of publication: Norfolk, Va., 1972 (Box 302)
  - North America News Service: Daily Release, 1973 (Box 28)
  - North America News Service: Digest of Revolutionary Journals from North America and Other Countries Place of publication: Boston, Mass. Publisher: N.F.C. Publications, 1973 (Box 28)
  - North American Anarchist Place of publication: Toronto, Canada Publisher: Anarchist Communist Federation of North America, 1979-1981 (Box 302)
  - North Carolina Anvil Place of publication: Durham, N.C. Publisher: North Carolina Independent Publishing Co., 1968-1983 (Box 303-308)
  - North Country Star Place of publication: Burlington, Vt., 1975 (Box 308)
  - Northcountry Press Place of publication: Minneapolis, Minn., 1975 (Box 308)
  - Northern Star Place of publication: Worcester, Mass., 1979-1983 (Box 308)
  - Northern Sun News Place of publication: Minneapolis, Minn. Publisher: Twin Cities Northern Sun Alliance, 1983-1985 (Box 308)
  - Northwest Passage Place of publication: Seattle, Wash., 1970-1983 (Box 309)
  - Northwest Passage Place of publication: Seattle, Wash. Publisher: Northwest Passage, Inc., 1985-1986 (Box 309)
  - Not Man Apart Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif. Publisher: Friends of the Universe, 1972 (Box 308)
  - Not the New York Times Place of publication: New York, N.Y., 1978 (Box 512)
  - NOW! Place of publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: National Welfare Rights Organization, 1969 (Box 253)
  - NOW New York Chapter News Place of publication: New York, N.Y., 1971 (Box 310)
  - NOW New York Chapter Newsletter Place of publication: New York, N.Y., 1970-1971 (Box 310)
  - NOW New York News Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: NOW-New York City, 1986-1990 (Box 310)
  - NOW New York State Place of publication: Albany, N.Y. Publisher: The National Organization for Women-NYS, 1976-1978 (Box 310)
  - NOW New York State Place of publication: Fredonia, N.Y. Publisher: National Organization for Women, Inc., in New York, 1976-1978 (Box 310)
  - The NOW York Woman [supplement to the "Manhattan Tribune," "Metropolitan Alliance," and "Majority Report"] Place of publication: New York, N.Y., 1971-1973 (Box 310)
  - The NOW York Woman: Newsletter of the New York Chapter, National Organization for Women Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: National Organization for Women, New York City Chapter, 1972-1986 (Box 310)
  - NOW-News Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: National Organization for Women, New York City Chapter, 2000-2005 (Box 310)
  - NOWNYC News: The Official Newspaper of NOW-New York City, the Founding Chapter of NOW Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: NOW-New York City, 1986-1990 (Box 310)
  - NOW-NYS Action Report Place of publication: Albany, N.Y. Publisher: National Organization for Women--New York State, 1985-1986 (Box 310)
  - NTEU Bulletin Place of publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: National Treasury Employees Union, 1977-current (Box 67-69)
  - NUC Newsletter Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: New University Conference, 1968-1972 (Box 253)
  - NUC-MLC Newsletter Place of publication: Madison, Wis. Publisher: New University Conference-Modern Language Caucus, 1969 (Box 253)
  - Nuclear Reactions Place of publication: New York, N.Y., 1982 (Box 309)
  - Nuestra lucha Place of publication: Toledo, Ohio Publisher: Farm Labor Organizing Committee, 1976-1983 (Box 309)
  - Nueva lucha Place of publication: Toledo, Ohio Publisher: Farm Labor Organizing Committee, AFL-CIO, 2002 (Box 260)
  - The NY Hackman Place of publication: New York, N.Y., 1964-1965 (Box 279)
  - NY Letter Carriers' Outlook Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: New York Letter Carriers, Branch 36, National Association of Letter Carriers, 1983-current (Box 290-291)
  - NY/NJ Teamster Rank and File News Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Teamsters for a Democratic Union, 1985-1988 (Box 292)
  - NYBC Update Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: New York Building Congress, 2005-2008 (Box 277)
  - NYEA Advocate Place of publication: Albany, N.Y. Publisher: New York Educators Association, 1976 (Box 487)
  - NYSUT United Place of publication: Latham, N.Y. Publisher: New York State United Teachers, 2012-current (Box 293)
  - NYU Inc. Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: NYU Inc., 2002-2004 (Box 260)
- O
  - Oakland Tribunal Place of publication: Oakland, Calif., 1968 (Box 38)
  - El Obrero de Area de la Bahia Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif., 1973 (Box 248)
  - Obrero rebelde Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif. Publisher: Synthesis Publications, 1979 (Box 313)
  - Observer, 1970-1971 (Box 309)
  - Occupied Wall Street Journal Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Occupy Wall Street Media, 2011-2012 (Box 311)
  - Occupied Wall Street Journal [Spanish ed.] Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Occupy Wall Street, 2011 (Box 311)
  - Occupy! Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: N+1, 2011 (Box 311)
  - Off Our Backs Place of publication: Washington, D.C., 1970-1988 (Box 311-312)
  - Office Worker Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Office Workers Union, 1933-1935 (Box 313)
  - Office Workers News, 1976-1978 (Box 312)
  - Offul Times / Offutt AFB, Omaha, Nebraska Place of publication: Omaha, Neb. Publisher: Omaha Military Project, 1972 (Box 164)
  - Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Union News: Official Publication of Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers Intl. Union--CIO Place of publication: Denver, Colo. Publisher: Oil, Chemical, Atomic Workers International Union, 1976-1984 (Box 313)
    Researchers must use microfilm (Film R-7069)
  - Oil Workers News Place of publication: Port Arthur, Tex. Publisher: Published by and for the Employees of the Gulf Oil Corp., 1941-1942 (Box 313)
  - Old Mole Place of publication: Toronto, Canada Publisher: Revolutionary Marxist Group, 1973-1977 (Box 313)
  - The Olive Branch Place of publication: Jacksonville, Fla., 1972 (Box 164)
  - Omaha Kaleidoscope Place of publication: Omaha, Neb., 1971 (Box 313)
  - Omega Press Place of publication: Koza, Japan Publisher: Omega House, 1972-1975 (Box 164)
  - On American Soil Place of publication: Durham, N.C. Publisher: Triangle Free Press, 2002 (Box 313)
  - On Gogol Boulevard: Networking Bulletin for Activists Neither East nor West Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Neither East nor West, 1988-1990 (Box 313)
  - On Guard Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Citizen Soldier, 1986 (Box 281)
  - On the Line Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: W.E.B. DuBois Clubs of America, 1969 (Box 313)
  - On the Move Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Metropolitan Transit Authority, 1983-1984 (Box 313)
  - Open City Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: National Caucus of Labor Committees in Coalition w/ Independent Student Groups, 1970 (Box 313)
  - Open Gate Place of publication: Stormville, N.Y., 1975 (Box 342)
  - Open Ranks Place of publication: Baltimore, Md. Publisher: Baltimore GIs United, 1970 (Box 164)
  - Open Road Place of publication: Vancouver, Canada, 1976-1988 (Box 477)
  - Opposition West Place of publication: Stanford, Calif. Publisher: Bay Area Coordinating Committee, 1966-1967 (Box 314)
  - Orange Empire News Place of publication: Garden Grove, Calif. Publisher: Communications Workers of America. Local 11510, 1984-1985 (Box 115C)
  - The Organizer Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Peace and Freedom Party, 1968 (Box 325)
  - Organizer Place of publication: Philadelphia, Pa. Publisher: Philadelphia Workers' Organizing Committee, 1976-1982 (Box 314)
  - Organizer / Communications Workers of America. Local 6360 Place of publication: Lee's Summit, Mo. Publisher: Communications Workers of America, Local 6360, 1974 (Box 115C)
  - Organizer: Building the Labor Party and a Worker's International Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif. Publisher: Socialist Organizer, the U.S. Fraternal Section of the Fourth International, 2004-2006 (Box 325)
  - Organizer: National Newsletter of the Organizing Committee for a National Workers Organization Place of publication: Milwaukee, Wis. Publisher: Organizing Committee for a National Workers Organization, 1968 (Box 314)
  - Orientaciones: órgano de la Federación Regional de Sindicatos de la Enseñanza del Centro Place of publication: Madrid, Spain Publisher: Federación Regional de Sindicatos de la Enseñanza del Centro, 1937 (Box 28)
  - Orthodox Marxist: Organ of the Homogeneous Party of the Working Class in the U.S.A. Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Homogeneous Party of the Working Class in the U.S.A., 1978-1988 (Box 314)
  - Other Stand Place of publication: Montreal, Canada Publisher: Committee for Social Justice in the Middle East, 1969 (Box 313)
  - The Other Voice Place of publication: Shreveport, La., 1970-1971 (Box 178)
  - Our Life and Times Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: New York's Health & Human Services Union, SEIU, AFL-CIO, 2010 (Box 315)
  - Our Socialism: Theoretical Journal of the Democratic Workers Party Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif. Publisher: Democratic Workers Party, 1980-1982 (Box 315)
  - Our Struggle = Nuestra Lucha Place of publication: Los Angeles, Calif. Publisher: Ricardo Chavez-Ortiz Defense Committee, nd (Box 315)
  - Our Times Place of publication: Toronto, Canada Publisher: Our Times Cooperative, 1982-1983 (Box 315)
  - Out Now! Place of publication: Long Beach, Calif. Publisher: Movement for a Democratic Military, nd (Box 164)
  - Outcry Place of publication: Berkeley, Calif. Publisher: Radical Student Union, University of California, Berkeley, nd (Box 315)
  - Outlaw Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: RAnk and File Mailhandler Committee, 1970-1975? (Box 315)
  - Outlaw Place of publication: St. Louis, Mo. Publisher: Outlaw Collective, 1971 (Box 315)
  - Outlaw Times Place of publication: St. Louis, Mo., 1971 (Box 315)
  - Outside the Net Place of publication: Lansing, Mich., 1972-nd (Box 316)
  - Overthrow Place of publication: New York, N.Y., 1979-1989 (Box 316)
  - Ozark Mountain Times Place of publication: Fayetteville, Ark., 1971 (Box 316)
- P
  - PACEsetter Place of publication: Nashville, Tenn. Publisher: PACE International Union, 1999-2000 (Box 30)
  - Pacific Tribune Place of publication: Vancouver, Canada Publisher: Tribune Pub. Co., 1977 (Box 325)
  - Pac-o-lies Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: New York Media Project, 1969-1970 (Box 316)
  - Painters & Allied Trades District Council 9 Spotlight News Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: International Brotherhood of Painters and Allied Tradesmen, 1973-1989 (Box 316)
  - Painter's Free Press Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Painters' Free Press, 1961-1972 (Box 316)
  - Painters' Rank & File Place of publication: New York, N.Y., 1961-1962 (Box 325)
  - Palante Place of publication: Bronx, N.Y. Publisher: Organización Obrera Revolucionaria Puertorriqueña, 1975-1976 (Box 318)
  - Palante Place of publication: Havana, Cuba, 1972 (Box 318)
  - Palante: Latin Revolutionary News Service Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Young Lords Organization, 1970-1974 (Box 317-318)
  - Palestine Resistance Bulletin Place of publication: Beirut Publisher: Democratic Front for the Liberation of Palestine, 1971-1973? (Box 319)
  - Pamoja Venceremos Place of publication: East Palo Alto Calif. Publisher: Peninsula Intercommunal News Service, 1971-1972 (Box 319)
  - Pandora Place of publication: Seattle, Wash. Publisher: Pandora, 1971-1979 (Box 319A)
  - Papel Chicano Place of publication: Houston, Tex. Publisher: Mexican American Cultural Corporation, 1971 (Box 97)
  - The Paper Place of publication: East Lansing, Mich. Publisher: Students of Michigan State University, 1969 (Box 319)
  - The Paper Place of publication: Morehead City, N.C. Publisher: Marines at Cherry Point, NC, 1971 (Box 164)
  - Paper Tiger: Radical High-School Students' Publication Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Andrew Schulman (Box 281)
  - The Paperworker Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: United Paperworkers International Union, 1972-1999 (Box 320-324)
  - The Partisan Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Youth Against War and Fascism, 1970 (Box 325)
  - Party Builder Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: National Organization Department, CPUSA, 1989 (Box 487)
  - La Pasionaria Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: NYU Revolutionary Women's Community, 1971 (Box 325)
  - La Patria radical Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: MLN, 1988-1993 (Box 325)
  - Patriot Place of publication: Kalamazoo, Mich., 1971-1973 (Box 325)
  - Patriote guadeloupéen: organe mensuel de l'Association générale des étudiants guadeloupéens, au serivce de la lutte du peuple guadeloupéen Place of publication: Paris Publisher: Association générale des étudiants guadeloupéens, 1972 (Box 325)
  - Pax Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: Chicago Peace Council, 1972-1973 (Box 325)
  - Peace and Freedom National Organizer Place of publication: Berkeley, Calif. Publisher: Peace and Freedom Party, 1968?-1968 (Box 325)
  - Peace and Freedom News Place of publication: U.S.A. Publisher: Peace and Freedom Party, 1968-1970 (Box 325)
  - Peace and Freedom Newsletter: The News from the San Francisco P & F Party Bulletins Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif. Publisher: Peace and Freedom Party, 1969 (Box 325)
  - Peace and Freedom Organizer Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif. Publisher: Peace and Freedom Party, 1967 (Box 325)
  - Peace and Freedom Partisan Place of publication: Calif. Publisher: Peace and Freedom Party, 1970-1971 (Box 325)
  - Peace and Freedom Review Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif. Publisher: Peace and Freedom Party, 1968 (Box 325)
  - Peace and Justice Place of publication: Los Angeles, Calif. Publisher: Peace Action Council (PCPJ) (Box 325)
  - Peace Courier Place of publication: Helsinki, Finland Publisher: Peace Courier, 1988-1993 (Box 326)
  - Peace News Place of publication: London, England Publisher: Peace News Ltd., 1954-1991 (Box 328-331)
  - Peace News for Nonviolent Revolution Place of publication: London, England Publisher: Peace News Ltd., 1976-1977 (Box 331)
  - The Peace Times Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Vietnam Moratorium Committee, 1970 (Box 325)
  - The Penal Digest International Place of publication: Iowa City, Iowa Publisher: Phase IV, 1971-1973 (Box 342)
  - Pennsylvania Labor Record Place of publication: Philadelphia, Pa. Publisher: Labor Record, Inc., 1943-1944 (Box 487)
  - Pennsylvania Union Labor Record Place of publication: Philadelphia, Pa. Publisher: Labor Record, 1943-1946 (Box 487)
  - Pentagon Paper Place of publication: Los Angeles, Calif. Publisher: Pentagon Peace Papers, 1972 (Box 332)
  - The People Place of publication: Palo Alto, Calif. Publisher: Socialist Labor Party, 1996-2008 (Box 327)
  - People Get Ready Place of publication: Francisco, Calif., nd (Box 332)
  - The People United Place of publication: Berkeley, Calif. Publisher: New Dawn Party, 1975 (Box 248)
  - People's America Daily News Place of publication: Cleveland, Ohio Publisher: American Communist Workers Movement (Marxist-Leninist), 1970-1971 (Box 332)
  - People's Anti-War Mobilizer Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: People's Anti-War Mobilization, 1981-1983 (Box 332)
  - People's Canada Daily News Place of publication: Toronto, Canada Publisher: Norman Bethune Institute, 1972-1974 (Box 28)
  - People's Canada Daily News Release, 1972 (Box 28)
  - People's Canada Daily News Service Place of publication: Toronto, Canada Publisher: Communist Party of Canada (Marxist-Leninist), 1972 (Box 28)
  - People's Herald Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: People's Herald, 1977-1979 (Box 332)
  - The People's Justice / National Lawyers Guild, Southern California Chapter Place of publication: Los Angeles, Calif. Publisher: National Lawyers Guild, Southern California Chapter, 1971-1982 (Box 331)
  - People's News Service Place of publication: Tucson, Ariz. Publisher: John Brown Party, 1971 (Box 332)
  - People's Press Place of publication: Clarksville, Tenn. Publisher: G.I.s at Fort Campbell, 1971-1972 (Box 164)
  - People's Tribune Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: Communist Labor Party of the U.S.N.A., 1974-current (Box 332-335)
  - Peoples' Tribune: The Political Paper of the California Communist League Place of publication: Los Angeles, Calif. Publisher: California Communist League, 1969 (Box 237)
  - People's Voice Place of publication: Edison, N.J. Publisher: American Workers Organization (Marxist-Leninist), 1973 (Box 238)
  - People's Voice Place of publication: Ill., 1971-nd (Box 336)
  - People's Voice Place of publication: Los Angeles/Bellflower, Calif. Publisher: C.P.U.S.A. (M-L), 1965-1968 (Box 336)
  - People's Voice Place of publication: Ocean Hill-Brownsville, N.Y., 1971 (Box 336)
  - The People's Voice Place of publication: Somerville, Mass. Publisher: People's Voice, Inc., 1973-1977 (Box 336)
  - People's Voice Place of publication: Vancouver, Canada Publisher: New Labour Press, 1998 (Box 336)
  - People's War Place of publication: Philadelphia, Penn. Publisher: People's Community Organization, 2002 (Box 336)
  - People's Weekly Place of publication: Waterbury, Conn. Publisher: Center for Black Development, 1972 (Box 336)
  - People's Weekly World Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Long View, 2007 (Box 336)
  - People's World Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif. Publisher: Pacific Publishing Foundation, Inc., 1981 (Box 336)
  - People's World (San Francisco Strike Bulletin) Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif. Publisher: Pacific Publishing, 1948 (Box 325)